Rabin Dhukhwa

4/67 Derrima Rd, Crestwood NSW 2620

Email: dhukhwarabin@gmail.com

LinkedIn: <u>linkedin.com/in/rabin-dhukhwa-8a5505156/</u>

Mobile: 0424521648

Professional Profile

I am motivated, trustworthy, and versatile. Master of Information Technology graduate from Federation University with experience as a junior software developer and IT support officer offering a solid academic and technical background with effective communication, information systems, and project management, where I can utilize my skills, particularly in coding to ensure efficient delivery of new and innovative technology solutions to customers. Customer-centric professional with a proven capacity to work with all levels of personnel and clients from diverse backgrounds. I am highly organized with the ability to take instructions as the plan to the required standards of the organization and to make sure all operations run smoothly. I am keen to join a team where I can further develop my skills and build professional relationships.

Technical Skills

Programming Language: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React.js, Node.js

Database Admin: MySQL, MongoDB

IDE: Visual Studio Code, Eclipse, IntelliJ

Hardware: Cisco Router, Switches, Hubs, Printers, Wireless Controller, Drivers,

Troubleshooting, Maintenance

• Software: MS Office (Word, Excel, Outlook, Power point), Adobe Photoshop, Server

(DNS. DHCP)

• Routing Protocols: RIP, BGP, EIGRP, OSPF, DHCP, ACL, and Static

• WAN/LAN Technologies: GRE, MPLS VPN, DMVPN, MPLS, Ethernet, VLAN, QOS

Security: SSH, Route-Map

Network Admin: Cisco, routing and switching, VPN.

Ticketing Systems: My Geeks Ticketing system

Education and Certification

ACS Professional Year Programme

Oct 2019 - Oct 2020

Performance Education, Sydney, Australia

Master of Information Technology

Jul 2017 - Jul 2019

Federation University, Sydney, Australia

Member of golden key international honour society

Top 15% academic achievement

Aug 2019 - Jan 2020

Cisco Id: CSCO13685130

Bachelor of Science in Information Technology

Jan 2013 - Apr 2016

Punjab Technical University, India

Projects

Designing e-commerce web application

Objective: Requirement of building a functional **Tools:** PHP, html, SQL, CSS, JavaScript

Duties: As part of a group of four my duties were to work on the design and development of the web

portal using PHP & html also software testing.

Result: Project was completed before deadline & achieved a high distinction for the final project

Professional Experience

Junior Web Developer

Mar 2022 - Present

IT Support Specialist My Geeks - Contract

Feb 2020 - Present

- Installation, Administration and Maintenance of multiple Operating Systems including Windows, XP & Windows 7
- Installing and configuring computer hardware, software, systems, networks, printers, and scanner
- Manage help desk team and technical team.
- Supporting clients via phone, email, remote site and site location, data entry, contacting the ISP for troubleshooting, installing, and configuring the company internal network
- Ensuring security of data, network access and backup systems
- Troubleshooting Hardware related issues
- Provided support (hardware/software)
- Roll Out from old machines to new machines.
- Image formatting, configuration, and installation of customer related program
- Configuration & troubleshooting Cisco device (Router and Switch)
- Supporting LAN/WAN/WLAN customers

Personal Attributes

References